<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>![RGON] T. Cain Rework</name>
    <directory>cain-crafting</directory>
    <id>3408837286</id>
    <description>
[b]
[h2]What's new?:[/h2]
RELEASE 1.3
Added several new performance modes for the mod, as well as simple quality of life and recipe balance changes. 
Item weights were adjusted, alt recipes added, and core recipes changed.
[/b]

[h1]This mod requires [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3127536138]REPENTOGON[/url]. 
If you do not yet have it, get it [url=https://repentogon.com]here[/url].[/h1]

Ever miss the days where Tainted Cain's recipes were stagnant and predictable? Do you feel recipes should be more involved and require a little more subtlety and nuance?

Look no further than [b]Tainted Cain Rework![/b] Tainted Cain Rework makes several changes to the Bag of Crafting, as well as Tainted Cain himself, enhancing the immersion and experience of playing the character.

[b]
[h2]Features:[/h2]
[list]
    [*] 380+ New Recipes!
    [*] New (and Consistent) Bag of Crafting Mechanics!
    [*] Involved Build-crafting and Item Synergizing / Strategizing!
    [*] Reworked Salvaging and gave the Bag of Crafting the ability to Salvage items.
    [*] More Unique Pickup Types in the Bag of Crafting!
    [*] Nuanced Recipes and Recipe Variety! (Recipes tied to aspects of the run).
    [*] Harder Late Game Recipes!
    [*] And so much more!
[/list]
[/b]

[h2]Notes:[/h2]
[list]
    [*] As stated above, requires [b]REPENTOGON[/b].
    [*] This mod has localization support! Currently, Spanish and French are partially supported.
    [*] Not all recipes are done yet currently. It may be a while until they are. Recipes subject to change for balancing reasons.
    [*] Incompatible with modded items and pickups unless they provide support. There is, however, an extensive API for adding support with other mods, such as custom recipes and pickup types, that anyone is free to use.
    [*] [b]An example mod is provided![/b] Be sure to check it out after playing the mod if it'd interest you to add more content. :)
    [*] [b]Only supports one Tainted Cain in co-op.[/b] This may change in the future, sorry!
[/list]

[h2]Frequently Asked Questions:[/h2]
[list]
[*][b]Q: What is this mod?
A:[/b] It's best experienced blind. :)

[*][b]Q: How do I consume items on controller?
A:[/b] Everything controller related has to do with RT. Hold RT first. To consume an item, then hold LT after pressing RT.

[*][b]Q: Does the mod have settings?
A:[/b] There is a Dead Sea Scrolls menu for the mod.

[*][b]Q: Is it / will it be available for Repentance+?
A:[/b] This mod is developed on the Nightly branch of REPENTOGON, and should work on it. When REPENTOGON releases for Repentance+, it should already work perfectly with it.

[*][b]Q: Is there a wiki for the mod, or a place to view recipes?
A:[/b] Not yet, but I am working with someone for this. If you wish to always view recipes, there is a setting in the options under Recipe Unlocks.

[*][b]Q: Why is x like this?
A:[/b] Balancing is hard. I want the character to be playable, but I want it to reward you with the good items you want whenever you know how to be advantageous and use your opportunities. If you find yourself struggling, think outside the box.

That said, the mod is still in beta, and I am receptive to criticism. I am aware of balancing issues, and am attempting to make changes to mitigate them, at least temporarily before I can come up with better solutions. Thank you for your patience!
[/list]
</description>
    <version>1.12</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
    <tag id="Shaders"/>
</metadata>
